我看不明白你的邮件
I didn't understand your e-mail.
你能再说一遍吗? 刚才断断续续的
Uh, can you repeat that? You're breaking up.
我看不明白你的邮件
I didn't understand your e-mail.
没错 我得稍微发挥下创造力
Ah. Yeah, I had to get a little creative
因为我键盘上的S R M键失灵了
because the S, R and M keys on my laptop stopped working.
"亲耐的Aby 嫩请你名田
"Deaw Aby, could you pleathe dwive be
开车松窝去活车站吗?
to the twain thtow thubtibe tobowow?"
你答应了吗?
So, is that a yes?
Sheldon 你干嘛不买台新电脑?
Sheldon, why don't you get a new computer?
你知道那台已经太旧了
You know that one's out-of-date.
但我喜欢这台电脑
Oh, but I like this computer.
画面快不行了 连声音都断断续续的
The video is failing, and the sound is cutting out.
抱歉 我没听清楚
I'm sorry, I didn't get that.
画面快不行了
The video is failing,
连声音都断断续续的
and the sound is cutting out.
抱歉 再说一遍 声音断断续续的
I'm sorry, one more time. The sound is cutting out.
我看不清楚!
I can't read that!
画面不清楚!
The video is failing!
买台新电脑
Get a new computer.
什么?
What?
买台新电脑
Get a new computer.
什么?!
What?!
喂?
Hello?
买台新电脑!
Get a new computer!
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第19集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酥酥要变瘦  校对: UUUU要翘臀
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
翻译: 酱油影 肉肉君 無限月讀 AU薇
太棒了
This is cool.
我俩上次一起搭东西是什么时候的事了?
When was the last time you and I built something together?
科学领域的话 已经是一年多以前了
Scientifically? A little over a year ago.
乐高的话 上星期就在我家搭过
LEGOs? Last week in my room.
如果你一上手就散架的
If there was a Nobel prize for Millennium Falcons
千年隼号模型能得个诺贝尔奖 那就赞了
that fall apart when you pick them up, we'd be set.
嘿 两位!
Hey, guys!
嘿
Hey.
你们怎么来了?
What are you doing here?
我们听说某两个性感的科学家
We heard there were some sexy scientists
- 奋斗了一个周末  - 没错
- working hard all weekend.  - Yeah,
带了些午餐给你们 一会我们就去找那俩鲜肉了
so we brought you some lunch and we are gonna go look for 'em.
浓汤 三明治 还有嘲讽
Soup, sandwiches and emasculation,
就跟我妈妈做的午餐一样
just like my mom used to make.
进展如何?
So, how's it goin'?
还不错 就是有点慢
Good. Slow.
有很多无聊的准备工作要做 但等弄完了
There's a lot of tedious setup, but once we get through that
进程就会快些
it should go quicker.
有什么我们能帮忙的?
Is there anything we can do to help?
好吧 这部分倒没什么技术含量
You know what, this part isn't that technical.
你完全可以做
You actually could.
真的吗? 你揭穿我了 还是算了吧
Wow, really? Called my bluff. All righty then.
我们真的能帮上忙吗?
Can we really help?
我们焊接这些主板的时候 如果你们能用特氟龙胶带
While we finish soldering these boards, it'd be great
把那些管件缠起来 那就太好了
if you guys could wrap these pipe fittings with Teflon tape.
我给你们示范一个
I'll show you how to do one.
嘿... 你俩潜心研究多年
Hey, w... wouldn't it be funny
万一我一不小心
if after all your years of hard work,
搞出个科学突破 会不会很搞笑?
I'm the one who makes a scientific breakthrough?
他觉得这一点都不好笑
He doesn't think that's funny.
我尽快赶过来了
I got here as quickly as I could.
你来晚了
You're too late.
Sheldon 这太愚蠢了
Sheldon, this is silly.
实验室的猴子死掉 你还伤心了呢
You got emotional when that lab monkey died.
那个实验室的猴子还用手势跟我表白了呢
That lab monkey told me he loved me in sign language.
好吧
Great.
这歌会在我脑海里播一整天了
Now I'm gonna have that song in my head all day.
听着... 请你
Look, I'm... I'm sorry
节哀顺变 但我觉得
for your loss, but I think
我可以送你样东西 让你感觉好些
I have something that might make you feel better.
我给你买了新电脑!
I got you a new computer!
你怎么能这么做?
How could you do that?
怎么做?
Do what?
选购新电脑是个非常私人的仪式
Choosing a new laptop is an incredibly personal ritual.
你夺走了我
You have taken away
几个星期的苦恼思索 繁琐调查
weeks of agonizing thought, tedious research,
优柔寡断的不眠夜晚 我...
sleepless nights filled with indecision. I j...
我今天失去的还不够多吗?
Haven't I lost enough today?
那个店员说这台很棒的
Well, the guy at the store said this one is great.
哦! 店员!
Oh! Oh, the guy!
不好意思
Oh, pardon me.
我... 还真不知道你会跟店员沟通呢
I... I didn't realize you'd spoken to the guy.
好吧 告诉我
Yeah, tell me,
那店员选的带4K显示器
did the guy choose one with a 4K display
和Thunderbolt接口吗?
and a Thunderbolt port?
- 有啊  - 是吗?
- Yes.  - Yeah?
那... 那店员选的电脑
D... Did the guy make sure
有1T的固态硬盘吗?
that this has a one-terabyte solid-state drive?
- 有啊  - 是吗? 好吧
- Yes.  - Yeah? Oh, well,
那店员是科罗拉多路电脑专卖店的Rick吗?
was this guy Rick from Computer Solutions on Colorado?
没错
Yes.
好吧 他的确挺厉害的
Yeah, well, he does know his stuff.
管身用反光带包好
After you wrap the body in reflective tape,
两端用特氟龙胶带包起来 这样就密封了
the ends get Teflon tape so we can get a tight seal.
- 像这样?  - 很好
- Like this?  - Oh. Yeah, perfect.
手指纤细还是很有帮助的
And it helps to have small, delicate fingers.
如果你没法做得跟我和Howard一样快
So don't be discouraged if you can't do it as fast
也不用灰心
as me and Howard.
我觉得这些焊锡不够我们
I don't know if we have enough solder
弄完这些主板
to finish these circuit boards.
我们昨天有一整卷呢
We had a full spool yesterday.
我能怎么说
What can I say,
我玩得疯狂 焊得更疯狂
I play hard, I solder even harder.
有时候他在家里光着膀子焊接
Sometimes he solders at home with his shirt off.
看着就像啤酒广告似的
It's like a beer commercial.
我们得去趟五金店
Well, we got to make a run to the hardware store.
连焊锡都没准备够你怎么好意思称自己为科学家?
How can you call yourself a scientist and run out of solder?
嗯 这是个有趣的故事 我们有很多
Well, funny story. So, we have plenty
锡铅比为60/40的焊锡
of the 60/40 tin-to-lead ratio solder,
但这圈焊丝看着就像63/37的...
but the spools look a lot like the 63/37 tin-to...
亲
Honey, honey,
亲 先别说了 这故事一点都不好玩
honey, let me stop you. That is not a funny story.
你想和我们一起去吗?
You want to come with us?
我正越卷越熟练了呢
I'm kind of getting into the groove here.
嗯 互换一下
Yeah, you guys run to the store
你们去商店 让女人们来搞科研吧
and let the women handle the science for a change.
好的
Okay.
我们会尽快回来的
We'll be back as soon as we can.
嗯... 所以说
Okay, so what...
焊锡是什么鬼?
is solder?
我认为我应该把它设置好
I suppose I should set this up.
还是你准备把这个乐趣也剥夺走?
Or would you like to rob me of that, too?
别烦人了 不然我就把所有的W的发音
Knock it off or I'll start making W-H sounds
发成WH
for words that just have a W.
你才不会
You wouldn't.
"宽着"
"Hwatch" me.
好吧 我很抱歉
Fine. I'm sorry.
谢谢你这个体贴的礼物
Thank you for the thoughtful gift.
我十分感激
I really do appreciate it.
你也知道 我很怀念我的旧笔记本电脑
As you know, I had become attached to my old laptop.
但我确定 随着时间流逝 它会...
But I'm sure, in time, that this one will...
天了噜
Jeepers creepers,
开机好快!
that started up fast!
我猜你就会喜欢
I thought you might like it.
看看这4K的分辨率
Look at the 4K resolution.
下次我们视频时
Next time we Skype, I'm gonna count
我准备把你鼻毛全数一遍
all those nostril hairs.
或者你也能凝视我
Or you could just look into my eyes.
但你只有两个眼睛啊
But you only have two eyes.
你的鼻毛可是多了去了
You got a lot of nostril hairs.
行吧 你开心就好
Well, you know, as long as you're happy.
我确实很开心
I am.
Rick说你可以把旧的拿去回收
And Rick said you could bring in your old one to recycle it.
哦 不不不不用了 谢谢
Oh. Uh, no, no, no, thank you.
但他说你可以换店铺积分
Oh, but he said you can get store credit.
呃 我... 我只是不想把它回收了
Well, no, I just... I-I don't want to recycle it.
我也不想要积分
And I don't want store credit.
但我们为什么不...
But why wouldn't...
我们能换话题么?
Can we please change the subject?
好吧
Okay.
那我们换成"你为什么这么不自在"怎么样?
How 'bout we change it to why you're being weird about this?
我没有不自在
I'm not being weird.
我...
I...
这不好解释
It's hard to explain.
Sheldon 告诉我吧
Sheldon, just tell me.
如果给你看的话可能会简单些
It might be easier to show you.
好啊
Okay.
我们得坐你的车
We'd have to take your car.
可以
All right.
我还需要你签署保密协议
And I'm gonna need you to sign a nondisclosure agreement.
我们一起睡之前我也签过
Well, I signed one before we slept together.
再签也不会怎样
Why not now?
Penny说她们建原型玩得很开心
Penny says they're having fun working on the prototype.
还记得以前她只有混夜店才开心吗?
Remember when her fun was nightclubs and drinking games?
我知道啊 我正在慢慢拉她下水
I know. I'm lowering the bar so slowly.
明年她就会有一整套硬币收藏了
This time next year she'll have a coin collection.
打扰了
Excuse me.
你们想免费看一个将要上映的电影吗?
You guys interested in a free screening of an upcoming movie?
哦 不好意思 不想
Oh. Sorry, we can't.
等等 这是什么电影?
Well, hang on. What movie is it?
我不能告诉你 但是是威尔·史密斯演的
Oh, I can't tell you. But it does star Will Smith.
等等
Wait.
我打赌这是自杀小队
I bet it's Suicide Squad.
我们去看看吧
Let's check it out.
那她们怎么办啊?
What about the girls?
Penny不是才说她们玩得很开心吗?
Penny just said they're having fun.
说实话 你想一整个下午都在那
Honestly, you want to wrap tape around
给一大堆管状元件包胶带吗?
a bunch of pipe fittings all afternoon?
好吧 我们去看
Okay, we'll take 'em.
但我发誓
Okay. But, I swear,
如果是鲨鱼黑帮2
if it's Will Smith in Shark Tale 2,
至少要达到他演的第一部那个水准
it better be at least as good as the original.
简直太疯狂了哈?
I mean, it's crazy, isn't it?
我从内布拉斯加来到这里想当演员
I moved here from Nebraska to be an actress,
现在却坐在加州理工学院的工程实验室里
and now I'm sitting in an engineering lab at Caltech
帮忙组装高科技导航系统的原型机
helping to build a prototype for a high-tech guidance system.
是很不可思议 更不可思议的是
It is crazy. It's also crazy
我已经卷了十四个而你才卷了三个
that I've made 14 of these and you've made three.
嘿 男人们都去哪了?
Hey. Where are the guys?
哦 他们去商店买焊锡了
Oh, they went to the store to get solder,
就是那种融化了能做科学小制作的金属
which is metal you melt to make science things.
你从什么时候开始周末也工作了?
Since when do you work on weekends?
我是天体物理学家
I'm an astrophysicist.
行星们可不放假
The stars don't take a day off.
你独自在家没人和你玩吗?
You were home alone and had no one to play with?
清洁女佣在那 但她不喜欢我
Well, the cleaning lady was there, but she doesn't like me.
需要帮忙吗?
You need any help?
我们可是有光速女王在这呢
Not with Lightning McQueen here.
我觉得我们能行
I think we're good.
好啊 没问题
Okay. That's cool.
我猜除了我大家都参与进这个项目里了
I guess everybody's involved in this project but me.
所以... 回见
So... see ya.
我好难过
I feel bad.
我们应该告诉他留下来么?
Should we have asked him to stay?
是啊
Yes.
你能告诉我我们准备去哪吗?
Will you please tell me where we're going?
不好意思 你只能知道你需要知道的东西
Sorry, you're on a need-to-know basis.
我正开车呢
I'm driving the car.
我需要知道去那儿
I need to know.
向右(向右和对的同一个词)
Right.
那么我们要去哪儿?
So where are we going?
我刚才是说向右转 你刚好错过去了
No, I meant turn right, and you missed it.
或许你的确需要知道去哪
Maybe you do need to know.
我们要怎么像女孩儿们交代?
What are we gonna tell the girls?
那根本不是事儿
It's not a problem.
我是说不撒谎
I mean without lying.
那就是个问题了
And now you've made it a problem.
别啊 咱俩聪明着呢
Come on. We're a couple of smart guys.
我们肯定能找到
I'm sure we can come up with a way to explain this
让咱们看起来有道理的借口解释的
that doesn't make us look bad.
噢!
Oh!
他们得开车去圣贝纳迪诺
The boys had to drive all the way to San Bernardino
买焊锡 结果胎破了
for the solder and got a flat.
他们相信了
They bought it.
我们回去之前
But we're gonna have to
得记得把备胎装上
put the spare on before we go back.
你蛮擅长扯谎的
Oh, you're good at this.
我习惯了胡说八道
Well, I lie a lot.
谢谢大家
Hey, guys, thank you
参加我们的试映 你们将
for being a part of our test screening. You're about
成为观看自杀小队的第一批观众
to be one of the first audiences to see Suicide Squad.
好啊!
Hey!
你做得对
You were right.
我不停跟你说
Oh, I keep telling you...
坏人有好报
good things happen to bad people.
几分钟后就开始 敬请欣赏
Uh, we're gonna get started in a couple minutes. Enjoy.
你给谁发短信呢?
Who are you texting?
Raj 他很想看这片儿
Raj. He really wants to see this movie.
他赶不上了
Oh, he'll never make it in time.
我知道 只是想让他难受一下
I know. I want to make him feel bad.
哈哈 我和Leonard要看自杀小队了
"Ha, ha. Leonard and I are about to see Suicide Squad.
剧透提醒: 碰见你的时候会给你剧透的
Spoiler alert: when I see you I'm gonna spoil it."
你真是最佳损友
You're a good friend.
好吧
Okay.
你们能先离开房间一会儿么?
Would you ladies please leave the room for a moment?
为什么呀?
Why?
我要用下面摩擦摩擦他们的模型
I need to rub my genitals on their prototype.
发生什么了?
What's going on?
Leonard和Howard不是胎破了
Leonard and Howard don't have a flat.
他们去看电影了 看啊
They went to the movies. Look.
混蛋 难以置信
Son of a bitch. Un-freakin' believable.
我要告诉他们
Oh. You know what? I'm gonna let them know
我和你们在一起 他们的牛皮吹破了
that I'm here with you and that they're busted.
别啊 别急啊
No. You know what? Don't. Don't.
先让他们觉得得逞了
Let's let them think they're getting away with it.
让我们看看他们能给自己挖个多大的坑
Yeah, let's see how deep a hole they can dig for themselves.
有意思
Mm-hmm. Interesting.
虽然没有蛋蛋放在恒温器上那么爽
I mean, it's not testicles on a cryostat,
但是我喜欢
but I like it.
为啥你有一个仓库?
Why do you have a storage unit?
等着瞧
Just wait.
你有这个仓库多长时间了?
How long have you had it?
等着瞧
Just wait.
需要我拿着电脑么?
Do you want me to hold that computer?
等着瞧... 算了 拿着吧 谢了
Just wai... You know what? Actually, yes, thank you.
欢迎来我的耻辱堡
Welcome to my Fortress of Shame.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这都是些啥?
What-what am I looking at?
基本上都是我曾经有过的所有东西
It's basically everything I've ever owned.
每本书
Um, every book,
每件T恤 每件坏了的电器
every T-shirt, every piece of broken electronics.
所有的
Just... all of it.
所有的?
All of it?
我有个保鲜袋
I have a Ziploc bag
装着所有用过的保鲜袋
filled with all my old Ziploc bags.
好吧
Okay.
呃...
Well...
我想告诉你
I would like to tell you
这没什么
that there is
好羞耻的
nothing here to be ashamed of.
我需要点时间适应一下
So I'm gonna need a minute.
他们回来后咱们怎么办?
All right, how are we gonna play this when they return?
我想到了
I know.
你们应该和我来一发
You guys should totally be making out with me.
亲爱的 我知道你觉得那样的笑话很有意思
Sweetie, I know you think jokes like that are funny,
但是你真的觉得能
but do you really think you could handle
一次性搞定我们两个么?
making out with both of us?
不能 女士
No, ma'am.
要不这样?
Okay. Okay, how about this?
他们不知道你和我们在一起
They don't know you're here with us,
所以你躲在柜子里 等他们回来的时候
so you hide in the closet. When they show up,
我们听听关于他们去哪了
we'll hear whatever their dumb story is
会扯些什么鬼故事 在假装相信他们
about where they were, we'll pretend to believe them,
等他们觉得自己得逞的以后 你再跳出来
and just when they think they got away with it, you jump out.
- 不错的主意  - 我喜欢!
- Yeah, that's pretty good.  - I love it!
我会说 牛皮吹破了!
I'll be all like, "Busted!"
他们会说 什么?!
And they'll be like, "What?!"
然后我们就说 耶!
And then we'll all be like, "Oh, yeah!"
我明白了
Yeah, I-I get it.
我也不会想跟自己来一发的
I wouldn't make out with me, either.
这里面是我用过的每一个收音机
In here is every clock radio I've ever owned.
计算器 录像带
Calculators, VHS tapes.
对了 还有
Yeah. Oh.
运动器材
Sporting equipment.
你会有运动器材?
Y-You have sporting equipment?
呃 只是个我哥哥拿来
Well, oh, it's just a... it's a... a golf ball
砸我头的高尔夫球
that my brother threw at my head.
你仍然能摸到凹痕
You can still feel the dent.
就在曲棍球砸出的印子旁边
It's right next to the hockey puck dent.
为啥你还有一箱子松果?
Okay, why do you have a bin of pinecones?
我小时候收集的
I used to collect them as a child.
它的鳞片螺旋是一个
The spiral of scales open in
斐波那契数列
the Fibonacci sequence.
当你把这事告诉你哥的时候
A fact that, when you tell your brother,
那边就会朝你头上扔过来一个高尔夫球
gets a golf ball thrown at your head.
为什么你觉得应该留着这些东西呢?
So, why do you feel you need to save these things?
我想说是因为怀旧
I'd like to say it's nostalgia,
但是每次一想到要把东西扔了
but every time I think of throwing anything away,
我就开始耳鸣
my ears start to ring,
心里也七上八下的
and I get butterflies in my stomach.
之后就感觉
And then it feels like
在胃里扑腾的小蝴蝶被老鼠给吃了
the butterflies get eaten by rats,
然后 老鼠又被...
and then, the-the rats get eaten by...
好
Okay.
我懂了 我懂了
I get it. I get it.
食物链的顶端是恐龙
It ends with dinosaurs.
如果让你失望的话 那我很抱歉
I'm sorry if you think less of me.
我没有啊
I don't.
真的吗?
Really?
因为我每次来这儿的时候
'Cause every time I come in here,
都会对自己失望
I think less of me.
为什么?
Why?
因为我是一个骗子
Because I'm a fraud.
不 我声称自己是
No. I purport
思想的巨人
to be a man of the mind.
(旧事物将被新事物完全替代)
是奇点理论的推崇者
I've been such a-a vocal champion of The Singularity,
但是如果我都没法把牙刷扔掉的话
but how can I leave my body behind
我又怎么能把肉体抛诸脑后
and become one with the Internet
和网络共生呢?
when I've never even thrown a toothbrush away?
没事的 Sheldon
It's okay, Sheldon.
你知道吗 我... 我也存了很多奇怪的东西
You know, I... I've saved a lot of weird things, too.
比如呢?
Like what?
嗯
Well, um,
你知道我
did you know I have a microscope slide
留着放有自己解剖的第一颗大脑的
with a little bit of tissue
一小点细胞组织的载玻片吗?
from the first brain I ever dissected?
我有一个偷偷用来擦鼻子
I have an old teddy bear
还擦了很多年的旧泰迪熊
I secretly wiped my nose on for years.
我们不是在比赛
It's not a contest.
他们来了 去躲起来
Okay, here they come. Go hide.
我出柜的那一刻
Oh, man, when I come out of the closet,
一定要狠狠搞他们!
I'm gonna nail those guys!
嗯 我听到了 闭嘴
Yeah, I heard it. Shut up.
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
嘿 这是什么?
Hey, what's this?
我们干了件蠢事
Listen, we did a stupid thing.
我们去看了电影还撒了谎 感觉很不好
We went to a movie and lied about it, but we feel bad
想补偿下你们
and want to make it up to you.
这些是送你们的 如果你们没生气的话
So, these are for you, and if you're not too mad,
我们想带你们去吃晚饭
we'd love to take you guys to dinner.
好吧
Yeah.
- 想去哪都行  - 好吧
- Anywhere you want.  - Oh. Well,
- 谢谢你的诚实  - 嗯
- thank you for being honest.  - Yeah. You know,
我是想生气来着 但是
I want to be upset, but we did
我们玩原型也玩得挺开心的
kind of have fun working on the prototype.
不要原谅他们 继续怒火中烧啊!
Don't forgive them! Stay mad at them!
他在那里干啥呢?
What is he doing in there?
搞你们!
Busting you!
没事了 他们道歉了
It's okay. They apologized.
对 没事了
Yeah, it's fine.
嗯 这有点反高潮啊
Well this is kind of anti-climactic.
你知道什么不反高潮吗?
You know what wasn't anti-climactic?
电影的结尾 听着
The end of the movie. Get this.
不要剧透! 不要剧透!
No spoilers! No spoilers!
他又回到柜子里去了
And he's back in the closet.
准备好吃晚饭了吗?
Ready for dinner?
嗯
Yeah.
我们要叫Raj一块儿去吗?
Should we invite Raj?
要
Yes.
所以 其他人都不知道这个地方吗?
So, no one else knows about this?
只有你知道
Only you.
谢谢你的信任
Thank you for trusting me.
如果不能对她发泄负能量
What good is having a girlfriend
那要女朋友还有何用啊?
if you can't unload your psychological sewage on her?
我就是你的负能量垃圾桶啊
That's me, your emotional outhouse.
嗯
You know,
如果你哪天决定了要来理一理这里
if you ever decide you want to do something about this,
我... 我会帮你的
I'm... I'm here for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我都不知道应该怎样开始
I wouldn't even know how to begin.
一步一步来咯
Baby steps, I guess.
嗯
Mm.
我想我可以试试把那个高尔夫球扔了
I suppose I could try getting rid of the golf ball.
好
Oh. Okay.
脑门上的坑就足够我记着这事了
I will always have the dent to remember it by.
你做到了
You did it.
你感觉还好吗?
Do you feel okay?
实际上 感觉挺好的
Actually, yes.
真的
I do.
为你骄傲
Well, I'm proud of you.
哦 谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
储藏室的事告诉了你 我很开心
I'm glad I told you about the storage unit.
感觉和你更亲密了
Well, I feel closer to you now.
我也感觉和你更亲密了
Oh, I feel closer to you, too.
你知道吗
You know,
离我上床睡觉还有好几个小时呢
it's still a couple of hours until my bedtime.
你在想什么?
What did you have in mind?
你太美了
You look amazing.
我想说 分辨率实在是太高了
I mean, this resolution is remarkable.
讲真让我回家就为了跟我视频啊?
I really had to go home for this?
对 感觉就像你人在我卧室里一样
Yes, but it's like you're right here in the room.
但是 我不在
And yet, I'm not.
感觉可以伸出手摸摸你呢
But I feel like I could reach out and touch you.
但是 你不行
And yet, you can't.
我知道了啦!
I know!